<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science Discovery on Twenty-Six.Two</title>
    <link>/categories/science-discovery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science Discovery on Twenty-Six.Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/science-discovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>/tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Ever wonder how the Netflix recommendation engine works or how Amazon.com determines what items “you may also like?” All these things are driven by training a computer how to learn using the large datasets. The data science course is a practical introduction to the interdisciplinary field of data science and machine learning which is at the intersection of computer science, statistics, and business. You will learn to use R to help you acquire, parse and model your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week One</title>
      <link>/tutorial/week-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/week-one/</guid>
      <description>Monday July 1st, 2019 AM: Instruction to Statistics  Introduction The Data Science Venn Diagram Class Survey Statistical Principles  PM: Introduction to Programming  Data Fundamentals - Presentation Slides Introduction to R – Presentation Slides (Data Camp) Introduction to R  Tuesday July 2nd, 2019 AM: Continue Introduction to Programming  (Data Camp) Importing Data in R (Part 1) Working Environments  PM: Continue Introduction to Programming  (Data Camp) Introduction to the Tidyverse Presentation on the Tidyverse – Hadley Wickham  Wednesday July 3rd, 2019 AM: Continue Introduction to Programming  (Data Camp) Data Visualization with ggplot2 (Part 1) Women’s World Cup Semi-Final  PM: Begin Introduction to Economics  Decision Theory  (Break) Why the World Cup Is a n Economist’s Dream (Ep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week Two</title>
      <link>/tutorial/week-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/week-two/</guid>
      <description>Monday July 8th, 2019 AM: Introduction to Data Science  (Movie) Titanic Machine Learning - Titanic  PM: Communicating Data  Introduction to Web Design in R  Resume Building Workshop  (Movie) Moneyball  Tuesday July 9th, 2019 Continue Introduction to Data Science  Tidy Tuesday (Instructors Choice of Options)  Kobe Bryant Shot Selection  Visualization  Wednesday July 10th, 2019 AM: Continue – Introduction to Web Design in R PM: Continue Introduction to Statistics  TBD (Netflix Algorithm) SVD v.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>