<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boston Marathon on Twenty-Six.Two</title>
    <link>/categories/boston-marathon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boston Marathon on Twenty-Six.Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/boston-marathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection - The Boston Marathon</title>
      <link>/post/boston/2019_reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/boston/2019_reflection/</guid>
      <description>As of April 20th 2019, I’ve finished my sixth marathon. No matter how the preceding 26.2 miles have played out, I’ve always been thankful that my body has withstood the distance and my mind has managed its aversion to suffering. It also feels good to stop. Unlike each of the six marathons I’d run before, my feeling upon crossing the finish line in this year’s Boston Marathon was absolute joy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacing Boston</title>
      <link>/post/boston/pacing_boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/boston/pacing_boston/</guid>
      <description>TLDR  This is the second in a series of posts on a data analysis of Boston Marathon. The first post focused mainly on particpants and performance. In this post we will look at pacing. How do runners pace the Boston Marathon? Are there significant pacing differences associated with gender and age? Does ability or finish-time influence pacing? How does hitting the wall impact pacing? We will attempt to shed light on these questions using a dataset of more than 70,000 finishing-times for the Boston Marathon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running With The Data, Boston Marathon</title>
      <link>/post/boston/the_runners_of_boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/boston/the_runners_of_boston/</guid>
      <description>A Data Analysis of the Boston Marathon TLDR  What happened at the Boston Marathon the past few years? In this article I present an initial analysis based on the data from this year’s event.
 For now we will focus on the participants of this year’s race — their gender, age, place of origin — comparing their participation numbers and finish-times.
   Introduction With the Boston Marathon quickly approching I thought I would write up a few posts on the data generated by the thousands of runners who completed the punishing course during the years: 2015, 2016, andw 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin in 2.01.39</title>
      <link>/post/berlin/berlin_world_record/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/berlin/berlin_world_record/</guid>
      <description>A Comparative Data Analysis of Eliud Kipchoge’s World Record at the 2018 Berlin Marathon A Brief Overview In the time since Eliud Kipchoge’s Breaking2 attempt on the Monza race-track in Italy, which secured him a place in the history books with 2 hours and 25 seconds over the marathon distance, he has seemed inevitable that he would go on to break the current marathon world-record, secured held by [Denis Kimetto] (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>